It ends.
It Chapter Two is a horror, thriller, drama film directed by Andy Muschietti.
27 years after overcoming the malevolent supernatural entity Pennywise, the former members of the Losers' Club,
who have grown up and moved away from Derry, are brought back together by a devastating phone call.
Beverly Marsh, played by Jessica Chastain.
Bill Denbrough, played by James McAvoy.
Richie Tozier, played by Bill Hader.
Mike Hanlon, played by Isaiah Mustafa.
Ben Hanscom, played by Jay Ryan.
Eddie Kaspbrak, played by James Ransone.
It Chapter Two is a 2019 American supernatural horror film directed by
Andy Muschietti from a screenplay by Gary Dauberman.
It is the sequel to It (2017) and the second of a two-part
adaptation of the 1986 novel It by Stephen King.
The film stars James McAvoy, Jessica Chastain, Bill Hader, Isaiah Mustafa, Jay Ryan,
James Ransone, Andy Bean, and Bill Skarsgård as Pennywise the Dancing Clown.
Set 27 years after the events of the previous film, the story centers on the Losers Club
and their relationships as they reunite to destroy It once and for all.
Talks for an It sequel began in February 2016.
By September 2017, New Line Cinema announced that the film would be released in
September 2019, with Dauberman writing the script and Muschietti to direct.
On a $79 million budget, filming took place from June to November 2018 at
Pinewood Toronto Studios, Oshawa, Toronto, and Port Hope.
It Chapter Two premiered at the Regency Village Theatre in Los Angeles on August
26, 2019, and was released in the United States on September 6.
The film received mixed reviews from critics and
grossed $473.1 million worldwide.
A prequel television series, titled It: Welcome to Derry, premiered on HBO on
October 26, 2025, with Skarsgård reprising his role as Pennywise.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
clown, carnival, sequel, remake.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.